The sea is so vast and nice.
Put a baby turtle on the mama's back!
Put a little turtle on the mama's back!
Splash some water on them, splash, splash, splash!
That's so mean!
Wait!
Hey!
Come on, keep your head up!
Apologize and I'll forgive you!
Say something!
What was that?
You little runt!
Back off!
I'll punch you!
Fine by me!
All right!
What is it?
What's this?
Swish, swish, swish... And down!
Look, it's not much, but I earned this money tending sheep.
I'll give you this, so please let Kogame-san go.
Only ten yen?!
Don't underestimate me!
Hold still!
I'll take you down!
I don't think it's right to pick on the weak.
I-It spoke!
I don't think fighting is good.
I don't think it's right to bully the weak. I don't think it's right to bully the weak.
Come on, pull yourself together.
You know, I thought I'd save Kame-san
and his friends, just like Urashima Taro.
But it turned out the exact opposite.
I've been looking for someone like you.
Please save me!
Save you?
Come, off to the Dragon Palace!
The Dragon Palace?
Whoa, this is crazy!
I have no idea what's going on!
I told you, I can't swim!
Sapphire!
Tink!
Lord Sapphire, where are you going?
I'm going to play with Tink!
None of that matters!
Be that as it may, Lord Sapphire...
Tink!
Wait up!
I'm not Urashima Taro!
If I go to the Dragon Palace, I'll drown!
Please, just bear with it a little longer to help us out.
But the Dragon Palace is at the bottom of the sea, right?
I'm scared of the ocean floor.
Sapphire! Help me!
Oh! Is that where you were? Wake up! Hey, wake up! Come on, wake up!
Are you awake?
Is this... the place?
It's the Dragon Kingdom.
So we really are at the bottom of the sea.
But I'm not drowning...
Come on, let's go to the Dragon Palace!
The elders and the Sea God are waiting!
The Sea God?
That's right, the God of the Sea!
A god?
Sharks! Run!
Wait!
I hear it, I hear it!
A ship is passing overhead.
Hey, sharks! Drag that ship down here!
Maybe I can eat some crispy biscuits for a change.
Hey, turtle.
W-What is it?
What is that tiny human you've got with you?
T-This is my guest!
A guest?
Don't make me laugh.
Give it to me! No way!
Shut up!
The more I look at it, the cuter this human is.
I'll put it in my zoo.
Hand it over!
No!
Wait!
Hey, Anko.
A little turtle and a rare creature came by, didn't they?
I don't know!
Don't play dumb with me!
I'm going to search you.
Human food.
Biscuits.
Soggy, just as I thought.
Ah, so noisy! I can't even take a nap.
Help me!
Who's thrashing around inside my stomach?
Thank you.
You saved me.
And now my stomach hurts...
Come on, let's go to Dragon Palace.
Here it is.
Dragon Gate Castle is really run-down, isn't it?
It used to be grand.
It ended up like this because of those Sharks. That's right.
Great Sea God, we have guests!
We brought visitors!
Great Sea God!
Haven't I told you that yelling will break the castle?
Ah, welcome! Glad you're safe. Hey, I thought Princess Otohime was at Dragon Gate Castle.
Princess Otohime is Master Monster's daughter.
Oh, so she really is here after all!
I'd love to meet her.
Princess Otohime isn't here.
Is he dead?
He's not dead!
It's just... What's wrong?
I am the Phantom Neptune.
Welcome, honored guest.
They seem like a kind-hearted person.
I'm Tink.
Tink, is it? You certainly don't seem like an ordinary human.
Get it?
Truth is, I'm not human.
I'm an angel.
Well, a former angel.
An angel?
Oh, what a blessing!
Sir Tink, please save my daughter, Otohime.
Save her?
What on earth happened?
Come this way, Sir Tink.
Right over here, Sir Tink.
Otohime is inside here.
Where?
I don't see anything.
Hey, is Ankou here?
Ankou!
Yes sir, right here!
Please give your consent.
She's really brightened up.
Whoa, that's a huge shell!
Princess Otohime has shut herself inside that shell and won't come out.
It's been a whole thousand years.
For a thousand years?
Why did you lock yourself in?
Something terrible happened a thousand years ago.
Master Tink, you are our last hope.
Please let my daughter out.
Mr. Clam, Mr. Clam, open your shell.
It's opening! It's opening!
Mr. Clam, Mr. Clam, open it wider!
No, close the shell!
Princess Otohime, w-wait! Don't close it!
Don't close it!
Mr. Clam, Mr. Clam, please open up. Lord Kairi wants to see Princess Otohime.
Hey, open your shell!
What's wrong with the shell?
Won't you listen to me?
Close!
Ah...
So, you're finally coming out.
I've been waiting for you, Princess.
Princess, Princess, why won't you come out?
It's your fault. What? "By her side"?
Get lost.
Shut up.
Now, where did she go?
Without Sapphire here, I'm hopeless.
Ugh, how annoying... Where could she have gone?
Heh heh, feeling lonely, are we?
Shut up!
My, my, I am Lady Sapphire's escort—that is to say, her bodyguard.
You've got no right to tell me to shut up.
I don't need a bodyguard.
Stop following me.
Heh-heh. As long as I trail behind, I just might get the chance to strike you down and send you to the next world.
Heh-heh-heh. Persistent and relentless—that's my best quality.
They say a turtle came to pick Tink up.
Yeah, he headed out toward the open sea.
Tink? Huh?
Princess Sapphire, where are you going in that beat-up boat?
I'm going to look for Tink!
Tink! Tink!
Heh-heh-heh! Talk about a stroke of luck!
That junk boat will sink before it even gets offshore.
This is the end for Sapphire! Ah, what bliss!
Tink!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Uh... wait, wait, wait...
Ah! Ah!
Hey, hey! Let go of me!
Sharks, you promised you wouldn't get rough. / Yeah, well you're the one breaking your promise!
I'll keep my promise! I definitely, definitely will!
You mean it? As promised a thousand years ago, you'll give me Otohime as my bride, right? / Yes.
His bride?!
Yes, absolutely.
Hey, I really love Otohime.
So, when will he show up?
By the end of the day.
He's useless. I can't wait any longer.
I've waited a thousand years for this!
I'll drag Otohime out my own way.
Yes, I'll definitely do it.
Wait!
I'll be the one to summon Lady Oto.
Wait.
I can't wait any longer.
I'm doing this my way.
Got it?
The nuisance is gone.
Now, please bring her out this time.
No, I don't want her marrying someone like Sharks!
That's Tink, isn't it?
Lady Oto.
You hid inside the shell because you didn't want to marry Sharks, right?
That's right.
But who are you?
I'm Tink.
I'll protect you, so don't come out no matter what!
That's Tink, right?
A promise must always be kept.
Why did you make such a foolish promise?
To stop Sharks' tyranny. He swore he'd stop picking on the weak fish if we gave him Otohime as his bride.
No way.
I'll never let them open that shell!
That's Tink, right?
It's to protect the weak fish.
Please try to understand.
Hey, turtles!
Let's all protect Princess Otohime together!
That goes for the weak little fish, too, right? That's right. Let's all fight together!
Tink doesn't know how terrifying the sharks are.
A ship is passing above.
That's right, sharks.
Drag the ship down!
And bring me a young girl!
Yeah!
Brother!
I just hope Tink is alive.
I just hope Tink is alive... She's a perfect girl.
Now, the Pearl of Forgetfulness. Forget everything, and do as I command.
There we go. Now come along.
Now then, let the fashion show begin!
Girl, put on the latest high-fashion dress and walk the runway.
Ah, alright.
Ah, it's Sapphire!
Wow, what a lovely outfit!
I'd love to show this to the younger princess.
(Laughs)
Ah, this is magnificent! The absolute best!
(Laughs) Buy 'em all!
Ready, set, go!
Sapphire, I'm so glad you came.
Hey, Sapphire...
Stop it! Who are you?
Huh?
Sapphire!
Don't just stand there, save the younger princess!
Master Tink!
Where could he have gone?
Lord Neptune, let's gather the fish and fight Shaks!
I'm afraid of fighting. Can't Master Tink do something with his powers?
Princess Ototo!
(Laughs) The wedding is about to start.
Good.
You'll behave yourself once we're married, won't you, Shaks?
(Laughs) Well, who knows?
(Laughs) Father!
Princess Ototo!
Fool!
What on earth happened?
Giving up without a fight... I just don't get it.
What are you talking about?
No, no... But I don't need a Sapphire like that anymore.
No, I hate you!
Tink!
It's Tink!
Huh?
Why are we in a place like this?
Hey, why?
Huh?
Whoa!
It opened!
Come on, Tink!
Hurry up!
Hey, over here!
Tink!
Here comes the bride!
(Laughs) All right, let's begin.
Do you, Shaks, swear to take Princess Ototo as your wife and live in peace without causing trouble?
(Laughs) Well, I swear.
Young Princess, living with Sharks as your husband may seem impossible, but do you swear to endure it and live in peace?
(chuckles) Are you embarrassed?
Do you swear?
Answer me already. I'm short-tempered.
Swear to me, my princess.
Come on, swear it!
Or else!
Oh!
Hey, over here!
Hah!
Put up a good fight!
Take that!
You're only tough when picking on the weak!
Attack!
Uoohhh!
(Laughs) Hah!
Charge!
Uoohhh!
Wow, way to go!
Oh, right!
Man-chan!
Show your face!
Hurry, hurry!
How's that?!
What?!
Daaaaah!
Hey, I'm so glad I called you!
Tink!
That was great!
(Laughs)
Thank you, Sapphire, Tink!
I'm ashamed of myself!
I completely forgot about fighting!
Huh?!
What's wrong, Sapphire?
This is terrible!
In Urashima Taro, one day in the Dragon Palace equals 50 years in the human world... Yikes!
That means 50 years will have passed when we get back!
Don't worry!
Here, take this treasure box with you!
I'm sure it will come in handy!
The treasure box...
Goodbye!
Sigh... I'm so worried. I wonder if all our friends have turned into old men by now...
Whoa!
Nylon!
What on earth happened?
Everyone is frozen!
What should we do? I-I'm kind of scared... Oh, I know!
Let me open the treasure box!
If we open it, smoke might puff out and turn us into white-haired old folks!
Well, I don't know about that!
What?!
Huh?
Phew, what a relief!
Yay!
Talk about a windfall!
Sapphire drowned at sea!
We'll make a fortune!
Look at that!
You two thought she was dead—so what's going on here?